Heather Dannyelle Thompson

Policy Analyst | MPP Candidate

From policy analyst to team leader, Heather's employers and community have come to see her as a fierce and reliable worker with whom they trust inherently in her ability to deliver strong and consistent results and add value. Heather's advocacy for Black and brown lives in Berlin and at her university has led to press coverage and a strong relationship with her university's administration to develop policy solutions to alleviate pain points. Through nurtured partnerships with multiple firms, a strong emphasis on research and storytelling, and a strong leadership, Heather lead the creation and product design of 'empower', a new corporate magazine to showcase the Data&Research sector of the non-profit.









heather-dannyelle.com shield-hertie.com



linkedin.com/in/hdannyelle

PUBLICATIONS please click for link

2019 Bangkok Startup Ecosystem Report

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

enpact e.V., Senior Research Analyst | Berlin, Germany 2019-present

- Lead author and analyst of the 2019 Bangkok Startup Ecosystem Report, for the Thai National Innovation Agency (NIA).
- Lead the redesign and concept creation of the 'empower' enpact branded reports to appeal to policy makers, entrepreneurs, startup ecosystem builders, and online content consumers. This new report debuts this month.
- Lead analyst responsible for drafting reports, creating content, performing policy analysis and policy consulting as well as team management and reporting.

ThinkLions, Managing Director | Remote 2019-2020

 Managed a team of designers, software developers, and researchers to deliver high-quality business plans and low-fidelity MVPs for entrepreneurs to develop their business, go to market, and secure funding.

 Secured high client success rates including a 13% conversion click through rates on their websites and to raise \$150,000 of seed funding for untested ideas.

IBM, Senior Cognitive Business Consultant | Washington, DC & Los Angeles, CA 2014-2018

 Served as a liasion and project manager between technical and business teams to deliver results for clients in insurance, biological sciences, telecommunications, and government industries.

EDUCATION

Masters of Public Policy Concentration: Policy Analysis

The Hertie School | Berlin, Germany 2019-2021

• Thesis: Is there a rurality factor in institutional police violence and misconduct? in partnership with Campaign Zero Publication May 2021

Bachelor's of Science in Material Sciences & Engineering (Double Major: Engineering & Public Policy) Carnegie Mellon University | Pittsburgh, PA, USA

• Research: A Plastic Bag Tax for Pennsylvania? and Local News in Pittsburgh in the Internet Age

LANGUAGES

Native









